A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Auxiliary Services FA845 FA845
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Auxiliary Services, Tri-Institutional Recitals
1996-1999
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
New York University
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
Cornell University
Cornell University. Medical College
FA845
0.25 Cubic Feet 1 box
1 box
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 871
Conditions Governing Access note
This collection is open for research.
Cell and biomolecular sciences; Biochemistry; Biology -- Research; Women’s history; Medical education; Medical sciences; Life sciences; Medical research; Architecture; Science -- Study and teaching; Women; Medicine, Preventive; Rockefeller University; New York University; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research; Cornell University; Cornell University. Medical College
- 1996 April (Box 1)
- 1996 July (Box 1)
- 1997 March (Box 1)
- 1997 April (Box 1)
- 1997 May (Box 1)
- 1997 June (Box 1)
- 1997 November (Box 1)
- 1997 December (Box 1)
- 1998 January (Box 1)
- 1998 March (Box 1)
- 1998 May (Box 1)
- 1998 October (Box 1)
- 1998 December (Box 1)
- 1999 January (Box 1)
- 1999 May (Box 1)
- 1999 June (Box 1)